friendmatrix.co 2013-10-06

# Social Matrix

Updated: August 2011

Social Matrix, Inc. and its related entities (collectively "Social Matrix", "us", "our" or "we") is dedicated to protecting the privacy rights of our users ("users" or "you"). This Privacy Policy describes the ways we collect, store, use, and manage the information you provide in connection with our website at socialmatrix.me (the "Site") or any Social Matrix application provided on other websites or other third party sources (collectively, the "Services"). Please note that the scope of this Privacy Policy is limited to information collected by Social Matrix through your use of the Services.

By using the Services, you are agreeing to the collection and use of your information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. You are responsible for periodically reading this Privacy Policy. If you use our Services after we have updated this Privacy Policy, you acknowledge that you have read the updated terms and consent to our revised privacy practices. Use of the Services after changes are made to the Privacy Policy will be considered your consent to the new terms.

### Information Collected and Used

The information we collect is used to improve the content and the quality of our Services, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We may disclose information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if Social Matrix is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Social Matrix will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
  * We provide such information to trusted businesses or persons for the sole purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf. When this is done, it is subject to agreements that oblige those parties to process such information only on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * We provide such information to third parties who have entered into non-disclosure agreements with us.
  * We provide such information to a company controlled by, or under common control with, Social Matrix for any purpose permitted by this Privacy Policy.

We may collect both personal and anonymous information. Personal information includes, but is not limited to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you such as your name, email address, home address, and phone number. When you access the Services we will ask for extended and special permissions from your Facebook account if it is necessary for the application. The permissions must be accepted in order to use the application. Please note that because third parties manage the purchases of virtual goods offered by the Services, we do not have access to your credit card details and billing information.

Social Matrix collects anonymous information, such as application use data and IP addresses. When you visit our website located at socialmatrix.me your computer's operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address, access times, browser type and language and referring Web site addresses are logged automatically. We also collect information about your usage and activity, such as number of clicks, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, and the date and time of this activity. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Services. By using the Services, you acknowledge and confirm that information about your usage of the Services can be used and archived. Social Matrix uses Google Analytics, a third-party tracking service that uses a cookie to track anonymous application use data.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We, and some of our third party service providers may, use cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, which is sent to your browser from a website's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are required to use some of the Services.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to Social Matrix applications and related sites. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Social Matrix and its ad management partners include, but are not limited to Google AdSense and LifeStreet Media (collectively, the "Ad Partners"). Our Ad Partners may use cookies to record current session information. Our Ad Partners may also from time to time use web beacons (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags and clear GIFs). These web beacons are provided by our Ad Partners and allow Ad Partners to obtain information such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page and the information in cookies set by the Ad Partners. Web beacons enable our Ad Partners to recognize a unique cookie on your web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our Services.

Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for your use of their services or for any use of your personal information by such third parties and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security practices as ourselves. The presence of a third party link within the Services does not represent an endorsement of the content of that third party's link and Social Matrix disclaims all liability arising from such content.

You can disable cookies on your computer in the preference or options menus in your browser. However, disabling cookies may prevent you from properly using the Services.

### Advertising

You should consult the respective privacy policies of our Ad Partners for more detailed information about their practices, as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, other advertisers or web sites.

### Data Storage

Social Matrix uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run the Services.

### Security

We take precautions to ensure the security of your personal information through the use of encryption and authentication tools. Once we receive your transmission, we will do our best to protect its security on our systems. Unfortunately, however, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to or from the Services, and you do so at your own risk. You should note that in using the Services, your information will travel through third party infrastructures, which are not under our control. We cannot protect, nor does this Privacy Policy apply to, any information that you transmit to other users. You should never transmit personal or identifying information to other users. ACCORDINGLY, WE DISCLAIM LIABILITY FOR ANY THEFT, LOSS, OR INTERCEPTION OF OR ANY UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS OR DAMAGE TO ANY DATA OR COMMUNICATIONS. BY USING OUR SERVICES, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE TO ASSUME THESE RISKS.

### Children

The Services are not intended for children under the age of 13 years and children under the age of 13 are prohibited from using the Services.

By using the Services, you represent and warrant that you are at least 18 years old or that you are at least 13 years old and have your parents' or guardians' permission to use the Services. We recommend that all minors 13 years and older seek consent from a parent or guardian before sending information about themselves to any individual or over the Internet.

### Changes

You may review, update, correct or delete personal information we receive from you. If you elect to register with us and you would like to review, update, correct or delete that personal information, you may do so by e-mailing us at info@socialmatrix.me and include sufficient detail in your email so that we may identify you and your profile. Social Matrix may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the email address specified in your account and by placing a prominent notice on our site.

### Questions

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be sent to info@socialmatrix.me or by mail at: Social Matrix, Inc., Attn: Privacy Policy Inquiries, 555 Bryant St. #325, Palo Alto, CA 94301.

Copyright © 2011 Social Matrix, Inc.
